fantasyfootballimpact.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Fantasy Football Impact

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for fantasyfootballimpact.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing** We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information** You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security** We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. For instance, Google ads (AdSense) use the DoubleClick cookie. It enables Google and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to our site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/ "Ads Settings") or you can opt out from some third-party vendors using cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/ "AboutAds").

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.

We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should[contact us](http://fantasyfootballimpact.com/contact-us-3/ "Contact Us") immediately.**

Go to the  **[ _Fantasy Football Impact_](http://fantasyfootballimpact.com/ "Welcome to Fantasy Football Impact")** ** ** home page
